<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>english on Luiyología</title>
    <link>https://luiyo.net/categories/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in english on Luiyología</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://luiyo.net/categories/english/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2019: Sunday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-sunday/</guid>
      <description>My Saturday finished having a great dinner with friends and lots of laughs in one of our favorite restaurants in Brussels.
 FOSDEM 2019 poster   As usual, my Sunday at FOSDEM started again very early. Lot&amp;rsquo;s of things to see in a complete set of new devrooms/tracks. This year I focused my second day in the Community and Geospatial devrooms.
Before continuing, if you want to read my summary of the previous day you can follow this link: FOSDEM 2019: Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2019: Saturday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-saturday/</guid>
      <description>It has been a week since I returned from another intense and thought-provoking weekend in Brussels, although it still feels like it was just yesterday. This year, apart from attending FOSDEM (as I intend to do every year) I took a very early flight on Friday to visit new (for me) places in the city. In just one day I visited the European Parliament Hemicycle, the House of European History, the Parlamentarium and the Museum of Natural Sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2018: Sunday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-sunday/</guid>
      <description>After an interesting Saturday, finished with a great dinner with some friends in one of our favorite restaurants in Brussels, my Sunday at FOSDEM started again very early.
FOSDEM 2018  My choices for the Sunday were again diverse and (in most cases) successful. Apart from the closing keynotes, I spent some time in the Legal and Policy Issues devroom, a couple of talks in the HPC, Big Data, and Data Science devroom and half the afternoon in the Geospatial devroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2018: Saturday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-saturday/</guid>
      <description>After an uncertain landing a few hours ago (the airport in Madrid was barely working due to a snowy morning), I&amp;rsquo;ve just arrived home but instead of having some rest after an intense and though-provoking FOSDEM I felt the urge to start writing about my weekend in Brussels.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been there not only to enjoy this wonderful city with its trappist beers and great food, but specially to attend FOSDEM as I intend to do every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Sunday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
FOSDEM 2016   You can read about the rest of my FOSDEM here:
FOSDEM 2016: Friday FOSDEM 2016: Saturday  As a retrospective, I attended a lot of talks and almost all of them were very interesting, but looking back now I realize that I should&#39;ve spent more time in the stands and aisles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Saturday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-saturday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
FOSDEM 2016   After an interesting Friday (as I told you yesterday) our FOSDEM Saturday started early. I attended a couple of talks in the Free Java DevRoom, another couple about Open Source Design but surprisingly most of them were in the Legal and Policy Issues track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Friday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-friday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
FOSDEM 2016   As you may know if you are reading this, FOSDEM is a not to be missed event about Free and Open Source Software (FOSS). By far, it is the most important gathering about FOSS in the planet. It&#39;s an unbeatable opportunity to attend great talks and workshops, but also to hang around with amazing people and top professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chaos by Gerard Nolst Trenité</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/01/chaos-by-gerard-nolst-trenite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/01/chaos-by-gerard-nolst-trenite/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve discovered through my dear friend Mónica a wonderful poem called The Chaos. I&#39;m talking about between 146 and 274 funny and well thought verses (depending on the version) about English spelling and pronunciation singularities written by Gerard Nolst Trenité which appeared for the first time in 1920.
I recommend as a splendid exercise that you attempt to read the entire poem aloud (aloud or do not try!). Everyone will get it wrong at some point for sure, but I hope you&#39;ll find it fun, challenging and educational.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God is not Great by Christopher Hitchens</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/12/god-is-not-great-by-christopher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/12/god-is-not-great-by-christopher/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be my first review in English. Don&#39;t Panic! As I recently only read and watch both TV series and films in English (usually without subs) seems to me the perfect way to express ideas and concepts from the books, as well as a way to improve my skills. Please help me notice any inconvenience or mistake.
I&#39;ve been constantly thinking about this post since I finished the book almost two months ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BoardGameGeek 2011 Secret Santa</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/11/boardgamegeek-2011-secret-santa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/11/boardgamegeek-2011-secret-santa/</guid>
      <description>(De ahora en adelante escribiré algunas de mis entradas en inglés, como simple entrenamiento y entretenimiento. A nadie le debería sorprender. Por favor, comuniquen cualquier error o incorrección)
One of the main (and marvellous) things about BoardGameGeek (BGG) is its Community. The entire website is built upon them, thanks to them. That&#39;s why I&#39;m part of it, I love it, help it grow, and cheerfully support it each year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>