<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on Luiyología</title>
    <link>/categories/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on Luiyología</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/programming/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Greach 2018</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/03/greach-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/03/greach-2018/</guid>
      <description>Greach 2018   Some days ago I attended, as usual, to the fantastic Greach Conference, an international conference about the Apache Groovy language and ecosystem: Groovy, Grails, Gradle,&amp;hellip; Greach is held each year in Madrid but everything is in English, and nowadays it&amp;rsquo;s surely one of the Top worldwide events about this technologies.
Greach is a non-profitable event is organized by Iván López (@ilopar) and Alberto Vilches (@albertovilches), with some help from colleagues and a lot of sponsors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2018: Sunday</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-sunday/</guid>
      <description>After an interesting Saturday, finished with a great dinner with some friends in one of our favorite restaurants in Brussels, my Sunday at FOSDEM started again very early.
FOSDEM 2018  My choices for the Sunday were again diverse and (in most cases) successful. Apart from the closing keynotes, I spent some time in the Legal and Policy Issues devroom, a couple of talks in the HPC, Big Data, and Data Science devroom and half the afternoon in the Geospatial devroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2018: Saturday</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-saturday/</guid>
      <description>After an uncertain landing a few hours ago (the airport in Madrid was barely working due to a snowy morning), I&amp;rsquo;ve just arrived home but instead of having some rest after an intense and though-provoking FOSDEM I felt the urge to start writing about my weekend in Brussels.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been there not only to enjoy this wonderful city with its trappist beers and great food, but specially to attend FOSDEM as I intend to do every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some things that Java developers really need to know in 2018</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/01/things-that-java-developers-really-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/01/things-that-java-developers-really-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago DZone published an article called 9 Things Java Programmers Should Learn in 2018. I liked the idea and I even recommended the article to a couple of colleagues who are trying to reorient their professional career. After the advice I added some personal disclaimers about the content, to the point that one of my friends wisely told me:
 if you don&#39;t agree with these recommendations, why don&#39;t you write your own article?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Spain 2017</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/11/big-data-spain-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/11/big-data-spain-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last week I attended Big Data Spain (BDS), a renowned event focused particularly on Big Data, Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning. It&amp;rsquo;s a reference event about Big Data, not only in Spain but across Europe. The event is almost entirely held in English and attracts top level speakers and public.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t take a lot of notes, but I&amp;rsquo;ll summarize the talks that deserve your attention (among those that I heard):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On being a Senior Software Engineer</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/09/on-being-a-senior-software-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/09/on-being-a-senior-software-engineer/</guid>
      <description>For many different reasons I have had to discuss quite a lot recently about the professionalism of some people, technical and non-technical. Sometimes, because a person feels that she (I will use the feminine as neutral gender) is not being treated fairly with respect of her category, or because her performance is disappointing for others, sometimes after unfair comparisons between colleagues, &amp;hellip; As a common element, a diabolical concept was almost always being misused in these situations: Seniority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ING Security Summer Camp 2017</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/07/ing-security-summer-camp-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/07/ing-security-summer-camp-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last week I had the huge pleasure to participate in a week-long Security Summer Camp organized by the Information Security department of ING Spain. The agenda was very promising and implied some theory and lots of practice, ending with an Escape the Room game and a 2,5 days long Capture The Flag hacking competition. Several speakers from the Infosec Squad prepared talks and workshops about different topics, focusing on Ethical Hacking, secure development, server hardening or OSINT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baking my Blog with JBake and GitHub</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/05/baking-my-blog-with-jbake-and-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/05/baking-my-blog-with-jbake-and-github/</guid>
      <description>Almost since I created my personal blog in 2003 I thought about moving it from blogger to my own domain, private hosting and so on. My lazyness prevented me from doing so. Not because the migration itself, but for the maintenance it entailed.
Anyhow, I was determined to migrate my blog outside of any blogging platform. I wanted to have complete control over my content, but without wasting lots of time in maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greach 2017, the Groovy Spanish Conference</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/04/greach-2017-groovy-spanish-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/04/greach-2017-groovy-spanish-conference/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll keep my intent to summarize all the important events that I&#39;m attending, and I&#39;ll do it again in English as the audience is international. Please, point me any mistake you may find  
Greach 2017   This week I attended, as usual since I don&#39;t remember when, to Greach 2017, an international conference about the Apache Groovy language and ecosystem. Greach is held each year in Madrid but everything is in English, and nowadays it&#39;s probably one of the Top3 worldwide events about this technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Codemotion 2016</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/11/codemotion-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/11/codemotion-2016/</guid>
      <description>Para mantener la buena costumbre (ya, lo sé, no siempre cumplo), voy a relatar brevemente mi experiencia durante Codemotion 2016, uno de los eventos sobre informática y programación más importantes del país. No hay números oficiales definitivos pero en la clausura la organización comentó que hubo más de 2.000 asistentes y más de 150 charlas/talleres. Suelo asistir todos los años, hay otros eventos más potentes e interesantes para tecnologías concretas pero como evento generalista donde puedes ver y oír de todo creo que Codemotion hoy en día no tiene rival (al menos en España).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greach 2016, the Groovy Spanish conference</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/04/greach-2016-groovy-spanish-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/04/greach-2016-groovy-spanish-conference/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll keep my intent to summarize all the important events that I&#39;m attending, and I&#39;ll do it again in English as the audience is international. Please, point me any mistake you may find  This last weekend I had the opportunity to attend Greach 2016. Greach is an international conference about the Groovy language and ecosystem, it&#39;s hosted here in Madrid but the conference is 100% in English to successfully attract top speakers and attendees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Sunday</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
FOSDEM 2016   You can read about the rest of my FOSDEM here:
FOSDEM 2016: Friday FOSDEM 2016: Saturday  As a retrospective, I attended a lot of talks and almost all of them were very interesting, but looking back now I realize that I should&#39;ve spent more time in the stands and aisles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Saturday</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-saturday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
FOSDEM 2016   After an interesting Friday (as I told you yesterday) our FOSDEM Saturday started early. I attended a couple of talks in the Free Java DevRoom, another couple about Open Source Design but surprisingly most of them were in the Legal and Policy Issues track.
This doesn&#39;t mean that this is what matters most to me now (and it matters, a lot), but surely there are other events to listen about containers, virtualisation, Java or Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Friday</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-friday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
FOSDEM 2016   As you may know if you are reading this, FOSDEM is a not to be missed event about Free and Open Source Software (FOSS). By far, it is the most important gathering about FOSS in the planet. It&#39;s an unbeatable opportunity to attend great talks and workshops, but also to hang around with amazing people and top professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tu tasa de paro</title>
      <link>/blog/2013/01/tu-tasa-de-paro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2013/01/tu-tasa-de-paro/</guid>
      <description>Algunos recordaréis (y los que no, ya lo sabéis) que en Julio del pasado año tuve el placer de participar en la PiWeek (Personal Innovation Week), una iniciativa muy interesante por parte de Kaleidos (una empresa madrileña orientada al software libre con la que tengo únótimë lazos). Esta iniciativa consiste en permitir cada seis meses que durante una semana completa todos los empleados de la empresa organicen y participen en proyectos totalmente personales (suyos o de otro compañero).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring I/O 2012</title>
      <link>/blog/2012/03/spring-io-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2012/03/spring-io-2012/</guid>
      <description>Por fin saco un rato, con un mes de retraso, para hablar del evento Spring I/O 2012. A estas alturas lo fácil habría sido dejarlo estar, pero en mi empresa me han recordado que por algo me &#34;designaron&#34; como representante y autorizaron mi asistencia. Como primer paso para compartir lo vivido con mis compañeros (en forma de presentación si sacase tiempo), dejaré aquí un resumen de las notas que tomé. Omitiré en el blog las anotaciones más técnicas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>