<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>page on Luiyología</title>
    <link>https://luiyo.net/categories/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in page on Luiyología</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://luiyo.net/categories/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Main public talks</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/talks/</guid>
      <description>List of the main public talks I have humbly given (in reverse chronological order)
   Title Details Presentation     Concerning Governance in Programming Languages, 2019 edition Commit Conf
(Madrid, Spain)
23/NOV/2019
Source Code in GitHub
Link to video        Design principles for an event driven architecture Commit Conf
(Madrid, Spain)
22/NOV/2019
Link to video        Omni-Channel Customer-centric strategies in a modern architecture Big Things Conference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Curriculum Vitae as a traveler</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/travel-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/travel-cv/</guid>
      <description>(Inspired by the CV Viajero by Dendarii)
Visited Countries  I have visited 20 out of 193 countries (among those recognized by United Nations plus the observer states). This is the list in alphabetical order:
   Country (visiting order) Main visited places (x times)     Andorra (#2) Andorra la Vella   Austria (#15) Romantikstrasse &amp;amp; Vienna   Belgium (#13) Brussels (x4)   China (#20) Beijing &amp;amp; Great Wall   Czech Republic (#14) Kutná Hora &amp;amp; Prague (x4)   France (#10) Annecy, Auray, Bayeaux, Bordeaux, Caen, Cancale, Carcassonne, Carnac, Concarneau, Dinard, Euro Disney, Fougeres, Grenoble, Honfleur, La Loire à Vélo, Le Mans, Mont Sant Michel, Morlaix, Paris (x2), Pointe du Raz, Pont-Aven, Quimper, Rennes, Rochefort-en-Terre, Rouen, Saint Malo, Tolouse, Vannes &amp;amp; Vitré   Germany (#3) Aachen, Augsburg, Bad Mergentheim, Bonn, Cologne, Dachau, Dinkelsbühl, Donauwörth, Düsseldorf, Feuchtwangen, Füssen, Landsberg am Lech, Munich, Nördlingen, Nuremberg, Rothenburg ob der Tauber, Röttingen, Schwangau, Tauberbischofsheim, Weikersheim &amp;amp; Würzburg   Hungary (#17) Budapest   Ireland (#9) Connemara, Dublín &amp;amp; Galway   Italy (#4) Milan (x2) &amp;amp; Rome   Netherlands (#6) Amsterdam (x10), Edam, Haarlem, Marken, Noordwijk, Rotterdam (x2), Utrecht &amp;amp; Volendam   Poland (#18) Austchwitz, Katowice (x2), Krakow, Wieliczka, Wroclaw &amp;amp; Zakopane   Portugal (#8) Évora, Lisboa, Sintra, Tavira &amp;amp; Vila Real de Santo Antonio   Romania (#19) Bucharest   Slovakia (#16) Bratislava   Spain (#1) too many   Switzerland (#12) Aareschlucht, Almendhubel, CERN, Chillon, Geneve, Gruyeres, Interlaken, Jungfraujoch, Lausanne, Meiringen, Montreux, Mürren &amp;amp; Reichenbackfall   United Kingdom (#7) Balloch, Bath, Birmingham, Blenheim Palace, Bristol, Cambridge, Cawdor, Cromarty, Durham, Edinburgh, Glasgow, Glencoe Valley, Inverness, Isle of Skye, Loch Ness, London (x5), Luss, Manchester, Newcastle upon Tyne, Oban, Pitlochry, Oxford (x2), Stirling, Stonehenge &amp;amp; Taunton (x3)   United States (#11) New York &amp;amp; Washington D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the author</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/about/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a Software Engineer, FOSS Advocate and Agile Evangelist habituated to lead and coordinate development teams for various environments.
 Luis a.k.a. Luiyo, the author   I&#39;m an active fellow of several national and international associations: ARP-SAPC and Círculo Escéptico (promoting critical thinking, in the former one as part of the Board since 2012); STE and AEFCFT (Literature and Arts); and AECC (about scientific communication and outreach).
I&#39;m also Member of Free Software Foundation Europe, OpenStreetMap Foundation, Spanish Red Cross, Doctors Without Borders, Amnesty International and UNHCR.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>