<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>page on Luiyología</title>
    <link>https://luiyo.net/categories/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in page on Luiyología</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://luiyo.net/categories/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Main public talks</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/talks/</guid>
      <description>List of the main public talks I have humbly given (in reverse chronological order)
   Title Details Presentation     Concerning Governance in Programming Languages, 2019 edition Commit Conf
(Madrid, Spain)
23/NOV/2019
Source Code in GitHub        Design principles for an event driven architecture Commit Conf
(Madrid, Spain)
22/NOV/2019
Link to video        Omni-Channel Customer-centric strategies in a modern architecture Big Things Conference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Curriculum Vitae as a traveler</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/travel-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/travel-cv/</guid>
      <description>(Inspired by the CV Viajero by Dendarii)
Visited Countries I have visited 19 out of 193 countries (among those recognized by United Nations): Andorra, Austria, Belgium, China, Czech Republic, France, Germany, Hungary, Ireland, Italy, Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, Romania, Slovakia, Spain, Switzerland, United Kingdom and United States.
 
In chronological order 2019  NOV Commit Conf, Madrid (Spain)
 NOV Big Things Conference, Madrid (Spain)
 SEP Amsterdam (Netherlands)
 SEP Beijing and the Great Wall (China)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the author</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/about/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a Software Engineer, FOSS Advocate and Agile Evangelist habituated to lead and coordinate development teams for various environments.
 Luis a.k.a. Luiyo, the author   I&#39;m an active fellow of several national and international associations: ARP-SAPC and Círculo Escéptico (promoting critical thinking, in the former one as part of the Board since 2012); STE and AEFCFT (Literature and Arts); and AECC (about scientific communication and outreach).
I&#39;m also Member of Free Software Foundation Europe, OpenStreetMap Foundation, Spanish Red Cross, Doctors Without Borders, Amnesty International and UNHCR.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>