<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>page on Luiyología</title>
    <link>https://luiyo.net/categories/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in page on Luiyología</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luiyo.net/categories/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Main public talks</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/talks/</guid>
      <description>List of the main public talks I have humbly given (in reverse chronological order)
   Title Details Presentation     Concerning Governance in Programming Languages, 2020 edition Congreso esLibre 2020
(Online Conference)
18/SEP/2020
Source Code in GitHub
Link to video        Concerning Governance in Programming Languages, 2019 edition Commit Conf
(Madrid, Spain)
23/NOV/2019
Source Code in GitHub
Link to video        Design principles for an event driven architecture Commit Conf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Curriculum Vitae as a traveler</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/travel-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/travel-cv/</guid>
      <description>(Inspired by the CV Viajero by Dendarii)
Visited Countries  I have visited 21 out of 193 countries (among those recognized by United Nations plus the observer states). This is the list in alphabetical order:
   Country Main visited places (x times) Visiting order     Andorra Andorra la Vella 2nd   Austria Romantikstrasse &amp;amp; Vienna 15th   Belgium Brussels (x5) 13th   China Beijing &amp;amp; Great Wall 20th   Czech Republic Kutná Hora &amp;amp; Prague (x4) 14th   France Annecy, Auray, Bayeaux, Bordeaux, Caen, Cancale, Carcassonne, Carnac, Concarneau, Dinard, Euro Disney, Fougeres, Grenoble, Honfleur, La Loire à Vélo, Le Mans, Mont Sant Michel, Morlaix, Paris (x3), Pointe du Raz, Pont-Aven, Quimper, Rennes, Rochefort-en-Terre, Rouen, Saint Malo, Tolouse, Vannes &amp;amp; Vitré 10th   Germany Aachen, Augsburg, Bad Mergentheim, Bonn, Cologne, Dachau, Dinkelsbühl, Donauwörth, Düsseldorf, Feuchtwangen, Füssen, Landsberg am Lech, Munich, Nördlingen, Nuremberg, Rothenburg ob der Tauber, Röttingen, Schwangau, Tauberbischofsheim, Weikersheim &amp;amp; Würzburg 3rd   Hungary Budapest 17th   Ireland Connemara, Dublín &amp;amp; Galway 9th   Italy Milan (x2) &amp;amp; Rome 4th   Netherlands Amsterdam (x11), Edam, Haarlem (x2), Marken, Noordwijk, Rotterdam (x2), Utrecht &amp;amp; Volendam 6th   Poland Austchwitz, Katowice (x2), Krakow, Wieliczka, Wroclaw &amp;amp; Zakopane 18th   Portugal Évora, Lisboa, Sintra, Tavira, Vila Real de Santo Antonio, Vila Real, Amarante, Guimarães, Braga, Porto, Póvoa de Varzim &amp;amp; Bragança 8th   Romania Bucharest 19th   Slovakia Bratislava 16th   Spain too many 1st   Switzerland Aareschlucht, Almendhubel, CERN, Chillon, Geneve, Gruyeres, Interlaken, Jungfraujoch, Lausanne, Meiringen, Montreux, Mürren &amp;amp; Reichenbackfall 12th   United Kingdom Balloch, Bath, Birmingham, Blenheim Palace, Bristol, Cambridge, Cawdor, Cromarty, Durham, Edinburgh, Glasgow, Glencoe Valley, Inverness, Isle of Skye, Loch Ness, London (x5), Luss, Manchester, Newcastle upon Tyne, Oban, Pitlochry, Oxford (x2), Stirling, Stonehenge &amp;amp; Taunton (x3) 7th   United Republic of Tanzania Tarangire National Park, Serengeti National Park &amp;amp; Ngorongoro Conservation Area 21st   United States New York &amp;amp; Washington D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the author</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Computer Engineering graduate, with strong experience guiding and coordinating high performance teams in strategic projects. My skills (emphasizing leadership, mentoring, organization and analysis) have led me to perform all kinds of tasks in addition to the purely technical.
I first learned how to code in the 90s (developing simple games in BASIC) but it was about 15 years ago when I started living on it first as a software engineer but very soon also as technical leader, team manager or software architect (usually with more than one role at the same time).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
