<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>holidays on Luiyología</title>
    <link>https://luiyo.net/tags/holidays/</link>
    <description>Recent content in holidays on Luiyología</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luiyo.net/tags/holidays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Japón (VI): Tokyo y alrededores</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/11/japon-6-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/11/japon-6-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>(tercer artículo sobre mi viaje a Japón, en los siguientes enlaces podéis leer el resto)
 Japón (I): paraíso de la tradición, la modernidad y el frikismo Japón (II): Llegada a Japón, Nagoya y Takayama Japón (III): Kyoto Japón (IV): Osaka, Nara, Hiroshima y Miyajima  TOKYO 28 Tren a Tokyo Shinjuku Godzilla Omoide Yokocho Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building
29 Meiji Jingu Yoyogi Park Omotesando Shibuya
30 Mori Art Museum National Art Center FujiFilm Gallery Aoyama Cemetery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japón (V): Himeji, Hiroshima y Miyajima</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-5-himeji-hiroshima-miyajima/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-5-himeji-hiroshima-miyajima/</guid>
      <description>(tercer artículo sobre mi viaje a Japón, en los siguientes enlaces podéis leer el resto)
 Japón (I): paraíso de la tradición, la modernidad y el frikismo Japón (II): Llegada a Japón, Nagoya y Takayama Japón (III): Kyoto Japón (IV): Osaka, Universal Studios y Nara  Himeji 24 Himeji Castle
Hiroshima 25 Hiroshima Highlights
Miyajima 27 Hiking en Miyajima
 - CC BY-NC-SA License    - CC BY-NC-SA License    - CC BY-NC-SA License    - CC BY-NC-SA License     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japón (IV): Osaka, Universal Studios y Nara</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-4-osaka-nara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-4-osaka-nara/</guid>
      <description>(cuarto artículo sobre mi viaje a Japón, en los siguientes enlaces podéis leer el resto)
 Japón (I): paraíso de la tradición, la modernidad y el frikismo Japón (II): Llegada a Japón, Nagoya y Takayama Japón (III): Kyoto  Osaka Osaka fue una de las ciudades que más disfrutamos, más allá de la parte cultural y monumental. Es conocida por su gastronomía y su ocio nocturno, y no nos defraudó aunque seguramente no fue en el lugar en el que mejor comimos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japón (III): Kyoto</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-3-kyoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-3-kyoto/</guid>
      <description>(tercer artículo sobre mi viaje a Japón, en los siguientes enlaces podéis leer el resto)
 Japón (I): paraíso de la tradición, la modernidad y el frikismo Japón (II): Llegada a Japón, Nagoya y Takayama Japón (IV): Osaka, Universal Studios y Nara  Llegamos a Kyoto a mediodía con tiempo suficiente para antes de comer llegar al hotel y recoger el equipaje en recepción (de nuevo, lo habíamos enviado el día anterior).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japón (II): Nagoya y Takayama</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-2-nagoya-takayama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-2-nagoya-takayama/</guid>
      <description>(segundo artículo sobre mi viaje a Japón, en los siguientes enlaces podéis leer el resto)
 Japón (I): paraíso de la tradición, la modernidad y el frikismo Japón (III): Kyoto Japón (IV): Osaka, Universal Studios y Nara  Aeropuerto de Haneda Nuestros vuelos de ida y regreso fueron al Aeropuerto de Haneda, uno de los dos aeropuertos internacionales del Gran Tokio. No fue por elección propia (es el que usa Lufthansa para volar a Tokio desde Europa) y no conozco el otro aeropuerto (Narita), pero diría que os recomiendo llegar a Haneda si fuera posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japón (I): paraíso de la tradición, la modernidad y el frikismo</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-1-paraiso-tradicion-modernidad-frikismo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2023/10/japon-1-paraiso-tradicion-modernidad-frikismo/</guid>
      <description>Llevaba mucho tiempo pensando en viajar a Japón, y a primeros de 2023 decidí que sería este año sí o sí. Empecé a planificar fechas y sitios a visitar y a medida que iba dando envidia compartiendo mis planes con mi entorno, uno de mis compañeros de trabajo y sin embargo amigo (Chema) me comentó: yo también llevo tiempo queriendo ir, ¿te apetece que vayamos juntos? y con las mismas comenzamos a planificar el viaje para los dos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pekín: una guía breve</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/09/pekin-guia-breve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/09/pekin-guia-breve/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Out of necessity, this entry will be shorter than I would like (although it may not seem so) and in Spanish, despite more than 90% of my readers (according to Google Analytics) do not have Spanish as their main language. For the first time I managed to take notes during the trip and I had to limit myself to transcribe those notes.
Nunca había visitado Asia y llevaba años con esa espinita clavada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The German Romantische Strasse</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/12/the-german-romantische-strasse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/12/the-german-romantische-strasse/</guid>
      <description>Some weeks ago I had the pleasure to make again an awesome road trip with my friend Agatha, this time through the German Romantische Strasse. It is not the first (and most probably will not be the last) trip together, you can read about my trips with her through Scotland, Austria, Brittany or Normandy (and we have made a few more).
I&amp;rsquo;m adding the German adjective to the title because last year I also traveled through the Austrian Romantikstrasse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featuring my new Travel Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/08/travel-curriculum-vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/08/travel-curriculum-vitae/</guid>
      <description>I was eager to introduce this section on this site for a long time, after seeing it on my favorite travel blog: Dendarii.es, written by my dearest Yami. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s about travels since I enjoy more and more traveling and reviewing my trips.
My Curriculum Vitae as a traveler contains two main parts:
 A Leaflet map with all my visited countries with a link to the review that I could have written here in the blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scotland: a brief opinionated guide</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/05/scotland-a-brief-opinionated-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/05/scotland-a-brief-opinionated-guide/</guid>
      <description>Some weeks ago I had the pleasure to make an awesome road trip through Scotland with my friend Agatha, my travel companion lately. You can read about our trips together through Austria, Brittany or Normandy.
It was my second time in Scotland, after a great trip three years ago to visit mainly Edinburgh. So, this time the Scottish capital was discarded as a destination and the goal was to visit as much as possible of the rest of this beautiful country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brittany: a brief opinionated guide</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/12/brittany-a-brief-opinionated-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/12/brittany-a-brief-opinionated-guide/</guid>
      <description>As explained in the previous post, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently been in Normandy and Brittany with my friend Agatha. After publishing the first part of the trip (Normandy: a brief opinionated guide) now I proceed to do the same with Brittany.
It has been quite complicated because we saw a lot of awesome things and for me it still takes a lot of time (several hours) to write this kind of articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Normandy: a brief opinionated guide</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/12/normandy-a-brief-opinionated-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/12/normandy-a-brief-opinionated-guide/</guid>
      <description>Some months ago I wrote in the blog about my road trip through the Romantikstraße in Austria. I shared the trip with Agatha and it went great, so we took advantage of the fact that we both had several pending holidays for this year and repeated the experience in two of the most beautiful regions in France: Normandy and Brittany. This post will be a summary of our experience in Normandy and hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to write a similar one for Brittany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (5 of 5)</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/07/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/07/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_5/</guid>
      <description>This is the fifth and last part of my chronicle about our trip through the Romantikstraße, you can read the rest here:
 Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (1 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (2 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (3 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (4 of 5)  Day 5 Our last stage started in Obertraun and ended in Madrid. After a fabulous trip around Austria, we decided to spent our last morning in a quite different environment, visiting the Mauthausen memorial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (4 of 5)</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/07/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/07/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_4/</guid>
      <description>This is the fourth part of my chronicle about our trip through the Romantikstraße, you can read the rest here:
 Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (1 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (2 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (3 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (5 of 5)  Day 4 Our fourth stage started in Gästehaus Lauterbacher, a splendid guest house in Neumarkt am Wallersee. Quite off our route because we couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anything affordable in Mondsee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (3 of 5)</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/06/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/06/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_3/</guid>
      <description>This is the third part of my chronicle about our trip through the Romantikstraße, you can read the rest here:
 Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (1 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (2 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (4 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (5 of 5)  Day 3 After two days visiting splendid places with invaluable surprises, we finally decided to discard a short visit to Salzburg in order to spend more time on each stage of our trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (2 of 5)</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/06/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/06/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_2/</guid>
      <description>This is the second part of my chronicle about our trip through the Romantikstraße, you can read the rest here:
 Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (1 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (3 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (4 of 5) Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (5 of 5)  Day 2 Kremsmünster For me, Kremsmünster Abbey was the most positive surprise of the entire trip. A priori it looked like yet another abbey, and our first hour there not only was confirming that suspicion but also made us feel somewhat deceived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Romantikstraße, the Romantic Road (1 of 5)</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/05/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/05/romantikstrasse-the-romantic-road_1/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I had the immense pleasure of making a road trip through Austria following what they call the Romantikstraße, Romantic Road or Romantic Trail in English. Interestingly, ours was a singles trip initially planned for three friends but sadly in the end we were only two because at the last minute Roberto had to cancel. I shared this great adventure only with Agatha and it was great (as expected).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Encuentro de Protos y Tip@s de Ludo</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/03/i-encuentro-de-protos-y-tips-de-ludo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/03/i-encuentro-de-protos-y-tips-de-ludo/</guid>
      <description>Aunque no puedo decir que haya viajado poco recientemente (y lo que me espera), llevo esperando bastante tiempo que llegue este fin de semana. Tengo previsto pasar del 3 al 5 de Marzo en La Almunia de Doña Godina (Zaragoza) con motivo del I Encuentro de Protos y Tip@s de la Asociación Ludo (Asociación de Creadores de Juegos de Mesa).
Esta asociación, de la que tengo el honor de poder ejercer de tesorero y que en si misma aún es una proto-asociación, tiene unos objetivos muy claros que podrán imaginar:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Descansando en la Costa Dorada</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2006/10/descansando-en-la-costa-dorada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2006/10/descansando-en-la-costa-dorada/</guid>
      <description> Nos pasamos por Sitges a ver A Scanner Darkly y compartir fabulosos arroces con el gran Txapulín y su amada Estela (Gracias mil):
 Un día y medio en Port Aventura:
 Largos paseos por las maravillas de la antigua Tarraco:
 Y una visita frikie antes de volver, la enorme estatua de Mazinger Z que ejerce de guardabosques en Tarragona:
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>En casa de nuevo</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/10/en-casa-de-nuevo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/10/en-casa-de-nuevo/</guid>
      <description>Parque de la Ciudadela de Barcelona  Hace unas horas que llegué de mi viaje por Barcelona. Tras darme un reconstituyente baño caliente, ponerme al día con el correo y ojear todos vuestros blogs, escribo un pequeño post de agradecimiento para que sepáis que llegué bien.
Tras un viernes agotador (salida a las 4 am, 6 horas de coche, 8-9 horas de feria, ducha rápida, y juerga hasta las mil) el sábado nos levantamos medianamente pronto para dar una vuelta por la Ciudad Condal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aniversario</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/10/aniversario/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/10/aniversario/</guid>
      <description>Brevemente, que salgo de viaje a Barcelona en 10 minutos.
Hoy, 7 de Octubre de 2005, ¡¡Luiyología cumple dos años!!!
Han cambiado muchas cosas desde el inicio, hemos pasado rachas de todo tipo, pero seguimos en pie luchando.
Gracias a todos los que solicitáis vuestras clases en esta humilde asignatura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marcho a Asturias</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/08/marcho-asturias/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/08/marcho-asturias/</guid>
      <description>Si consigo escaparme del trabajo mañana iniciaré mi peregrinación habitual por estas fechas a mi segunda patria en tierras asturianas.
Vuelvo a llevar conmigo al ínclito Finceleb, que ya me acompañó el año pasado al Descenso del Sella. La explosión aquel día de un artefacto terrorista a pocos metros de nosotros no le ha desanimado. Habrá ayudado el hecho de que nos pilló jugando a las palas en la playa junto a dos cajas de sidra XDD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toledo muy medieval</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/04/toledo-muy-medieval/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/04/toledo-muy-medieval/</guid>
      <description>La Catedral de Toledo reflejada en Don Quijote  El Viernes pase el día en Toledo. Volví a pasear por sus calles, siempre rodeado de esa enorme cantidad de acero. Es impresionante.
La ciudad es ciertamente bonita, pero es el ambiente lo que me hace volver de cuando en cuando. Tanto, que un día que vuelva tendré que plantearme dejarme de paseos y entrar a visitar los edificios importantes y museos, que tras muchas visitas aún desconozco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fin de Semana en Jerez</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/04/fin-de-semana-en-jerez/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2005/04/fin-de-semana-en-jerez/</guid>
      <description>Escudo de Jerez de la Frontera  Siempre me han encantado las motos. Diría mejor el motociclismo, pues apenas he conducido un par de veces una moto pequeñita.
Este fin de semana he cumplido varios de mis deseos, disfrutar de un fabuloso fin de semana en Jerez, hacerlo durante un Gran Premio de Motociclismo, ver Sevilla, conocer más el Sur y encontrar gente estupenda.
Salimos de Madrid el Viernes muy temprano, y llegamos a comer a Sevilla.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
