<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>internet on Luiyología</title>
    <link>https://luiyo.net/tags/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in internet on Luiyología</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://luiyo.net/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2020, 20 Years of FOSDEM</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2020/02/fosdem-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2020/02/fosdem-2020/</guid>
      <description>It has been almost a month since I returned from another intense and thought-provoking weekend in Brussels, although it still feels like it was just yesterday. I couldn&#39;t write this before, as I have been quite busy both at work and at home.
 FOSDEM 2020 poster   For those of you who don&#39;t know FOSDEM, it is the biggest conference in Europe (and one of the biggest around the world) related to Open Source development and communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Things Conference and Commit Conf 2019</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/12/big-things-commit-conf-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/12/big-things-commit-conf-2019/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I had the opportunity and the privilege to deliver three different talks, in three consecutive days, in two international events: Big Things Conference 2019 and Commit Conf 2019. This crazy coincidence forces me to write one single post to summarize my experience in both events, including an overview of my three talks.
Taking advantage of this, I have also created a new section on this website to publish the main public talks that I&#39;m proudly giving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greach 2019</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/03/greach-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/03/greach-2019/</guid>
      <description>Greach 2019   This week I could attend another fantastic Greach Conference, an international conference that in previous years was focused on the Apache Groovy language and ecosystem (Grails, Gradle, etc.) but this year has expanded the scope to other technologies related to the JVM like Micronaut, GraalVM, Spring Boot, Kotlin, Android, &amp;hellip;
Greach is a non-profitable event held in Madrid since 2011 (I think I&#39;ve missed only one edition).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2019: Sunday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-sunday/</guid>
      <description>My Saturday finished having a great dinner with friends and lots of laughs in one of our favorite restaurants in Brussels.
 FOSDEM 2019 poster   As usual, my Sunday at FOSDEM started again very early. Lot&#39;s of things to see in a complete set of new devrooms/tracks. This year I focused my second day in the Community and Geospatial devrooms.
Before continuing, if you want to read my summary of the previous day you can follow this link: FOSDEM 2019: Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2019: Saturday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2019/02/fosdem-2019-saturday/</guid>
      <description>It has been a week since I returned from another intense and thought-provoking weekend in Brussels, although it still feels like it was just yesterday. This year, apart from attending FOSDEM (as I intend to do every year) I took a very early flight on Friday to visit new (for me) places in the city. In just one day I visited the European Parliament Hemicycle, the House of European History, the Parlamentarium and the Museum of Natural Sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greach 2018</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/03/greach-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/03/greach-2018/</guid>
      <description>Greach 2018   Some days ago I attended as usual to the fantastic Greach Conference, an international conference about the Apache Groovy language and ecosystem: Groovy, Grails, Gradle and a lot other things. Greach is held each year in Madrid but everything is in English, and nowadays it&#39;s surely one of the Top worldwide events about this technologies.
Greach is a non-profitable event organized by Iván López (@ilopar) and Alberto Vilches (@albertovilches), with some help from colleagues and a lot of sponsors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2018: Sunday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-sunday/</guid>
      <description>After an interesting Saturday, finished with a great dinner with some friends in one of our favorite restaurants in Brussels, my Sunday at FOSDEM started again very early.
FOSDEM 2018  My choices for the Sunday were again diverse and (in most cases) successful. Apart from the closing keynotes, I spent some time in the Legal and Policy Issues devroom, a couple of talks in the HPC, Big Data, and Data Science devroom and half the afternoon in the Geospatial devroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2018: Saturday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2018/02/fosdem-2018-saturday/</guid>
      <description>After an uncertain landing a few hours ago (the airport in Madrid was barely working due to a snowy morning), I&#39;ve just arrived home but instead of having some rest after an intense and though-provoking FOSDEM I felt the urge to start writing about my weekend in Brussels.
I&#39;ve been there not only to enjoy this wonderful city with its trappist beers and great food, but specially to attend FOSDEM as I intend to do every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ING Security Summer Camp 2017</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/07/ing-security-summer-camp-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/07/ing-security-summer-camp-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last week I had the huge pleasure to participate in a week-long Security Summer Camp organized by the Information Security department of ING Spain. The agenda was very promising and implied some theory and lots of practice, ending with an Escape the Room game and a 2,5 days long Capture The Flag hacking competition. Several speakers from the Infosec Squad prepared talks and workshops about different topics, focusing on Ethical Hacking, secure development, server hardening or OSINT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greach 2017, the Groovy Spanish Conference</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/04/greach-2017-groovy-spanish-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2017/04/greach-2017-groovy-spanish-conference/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll keep my intent to summarize all the important events that I&#39;m attending, and I&#39;ll do it again in English as the audience is international. Please, point me any mistake you may find  
 Greach Conference 2017   This week I attended, as usual since I don&#39;t remember when, to Greach 2017, an international conference about the Apache Groovy language and ecosystem. Greach is held each year in Madrid but everything is in English, and nowadays it&#39;s probably one of the Top3 worldwide events about this technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Codemotion 2016</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/11/codemotion-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/11/codemotion-2016/</guid>
      <description>Para mantener la buena costumbre (ya, lo sé, no siempre cumplo), voy a relatar brevemente mi experiencia durante Codemotion 2016, uno de los eventos sobre informática y programación más importantes del país. No hay números oficiales definitivos pero en la clausura la organización comentó que hubo más de 2.000 asistentes y más de 150 charlas/talleres. Suelo asistir todos los años, hay otros eventos más potentes e interesantes para tecnologías concretas pero como evento generalista donde puedes ver y oír de todo creo que Codemotion hoy en día no tiene rival (al menos en España).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greach 2016, the Groovy Spanish conference</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/04/greach-2016-groovy-spanish-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/04/greach-2016-groovy-spanish-conference/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ll keep my intent to summarize all the important events that I&#39;m attending, and I&#39;ll do it again in English as the audience is international. Please, point me any mistake you may find  This last weekend I had the opportunity to attend Greach 2016. Greach is an international conference about the Groovy language and ecosystem, it&#39;s hosted here in Madrid but the conference is 100% in English to successfully attract top speakers and attendees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Sunday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-sunday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
 FOSDEM 2016   You can read about the rest of my FOSDEM here:
FOSDEM 2016: Friday FOSDEM 2016: Saturday  As a retrospective, I attended a lot of talks and almost all of them were very interesting, but looking back now I realize that I should&#39;ve spent more time in the stands and aisles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Saturday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-saturday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
 FOSDEM 2016   After an interesting Friday (as I told you yesterday) our FOSDEM Saturday started early. I attended a couple of talks in the Free Java DevRoom, another couple about Open Source Design but surprisingly most of them were in the Legal and Policy Issues track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM 2016: Friday</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2016/03/fosdem-2016-friday/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I attended FOSDEM in Brussels last January. I should have written this weeks ago but better late than ever, right?
 FOSDEM 2016   As you may know if you are reading this, FOSDEM is a not to be missed event about Free and Open Source Software (FOSS). By far, it is the most important gathering about FOSS in the planet. It&#39;s an unbeatable opportunity to attend great talks and workshops, but also to hang around with amazing people and top professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escépticos en el Pub Madrid - Enero 2015</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2014/12/escepticos-en-el-pub-madrid-enero-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2014/12/escepticos-en-el-pub-madrid-enero-2015/</guid>
      <description>(mientras pienso si retomo la costumbre de publicar aquí también las convocatorias de EeeP Madrid, les dejo una que no deben perderse)  Arrancaremos el nuevo año en Escépticos en el Pub Madrid con un evento que esperamos os resulte tan interesante como a nosotros sobre periodismo de datos y la necesidad ciudadana de contrastar críticamente la información que recibe. Para ello, el Sábado 10 de Enero de 2015 nos visitan David Cabo y Eva Belmonte con una charla titulada Periodismo para gente incrédula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crónica de una visita guiada al CERN</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2013/02/cronica-de-una-visita-guiada-al-cern/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2013/02/cronica-de-una-visita-guiada-al-cern/</guid>
      <description>(Entrada publicada también en el blog de la Asociación Española de Comunicación Científica)  Hace unos días publiqué una Guía para visitar el CERN que tuvo bastante éxito y mucha gente me ha solicitado más información sobre la visita. Para completar en lo posible, aunque sin entrar a valorar aquello que puede encontrarse fácilmente en Google sobre el CERN, voy a relatar mi visita añadiendo toda la información de tipo práctico que crea útil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guía para visitar el CERN</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2013/01/guia-para-visitar-el-cern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2013/01/guia-para-visitar-el-cern/</guid>
      <description>(Entrada publicada también en el blog de la Asociación Española de Comunicación Científica)  Dentro de tres días, el próximo Miércoles 30 de Enero, estaré en Ginebra para una visita que llevo mucho tiempo planeando: la Organización Europea para la Investigación Nuclear que todos conocemos por sus siglas en francés CERN (Conseil Européen pour la Recherche Nucléaire).
Tras una introducción para despistados (muy despistados) entraré al propósito de esta entrada, una guía rápida y fácil para visitar el CERN, dado que es mucho más sencillo y asequible de lo que la gente cree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>III Congreso El Ser Creativo</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/11/iii-congreso-el-ser-creativo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/11/iii-congreso-el-ser-creativo/</guid>
      <description>Al igual que el pasado año, esta semana voy a tener el privilegio de asistir como invitado a El Ser Creativo, III Congreso de Mentes Brillantes, que se celebrará el 6 y 7 de Noviembre en Madrid. De nuevo tendré la misión de cubrir el evento a través de @escepticos, el Twitter de ARP-SAPC (Sociedad para el Avance del Pensamiento Crítico), haré muchas fotos y posteriormente ayudaré a redactar la crónica para la revista El Escéptico de ARP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring I/O 2012</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/03/spring-io-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/03/spring-io-2012/</guid>
      <description>Por fin saco un rato, con un mes de retraso, para hablar del evento Spring I/O 2012. A estas alturas lo fácil habría sido dejarlo estar, pero en mi empresa me han recordado que por algo me &#34;designaron&#34; como representante y autorizaron mi asistencia. Como primer paso para compartir lo vivido con mis compañeros (en forma de presentación si sacase tiempo), dejaré aquí un resumen de las notas que tomé.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Escépticos en el Pub Madrid - Marzo 2012</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/03/escepticos-en-el-pub-madrid-marzo-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/03/escepticos-en-el-pub-madrid-marzo-2012/</guid>
      <description>En Febrero hicimos doblete y tuvimos dos ediciones épicas de Escépticos en el Pub Madrid. Como la segunda de ellas fue este pasado fin de semana, en Marzo retrasamos el evento del habitual primer sábado al segundo.
Javier de la Cueva, abogado especialista en propiedad intelectual y autor del blog Derecho de Internet, nos hablará de su especialidad haciendo un amplio (y muy necesario) repaso al asunto. En sus propias palabras:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divulgación 2.0, de todos y para todos</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/02/divulgacion-20-de-todos-y-para-todos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/02/divulgacion-20-de-todos-y-para-todos/</guid>
      <description>(Esta entrada se publicó hace 24 horas en el blog de Street Alicante Science)
Hasta hace poco la divulgación en este país se hacia para unos pocos y habitualmente también se originaba en unos pocos. Gracias al imparable desarrollo de Internet y la sociedad de la información, esto afortunadamente también se ha democratizado y vemos como día a día sigue en un crecimiento imparable hasta ahora e inimaginable hace unos años.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SkeptiCamp, eventos abiertos de divulgación</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/02/skepticamp-eventos-abiertos-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/02/skepticamp-eventos-abiertos-de/</guid>
      <description>(Entrada publicada originalmente en el blog de la Asociación Española de Comunicación Científica, asociación a la cual tengo el gusto y el honor de haber sido invitado a pertenecer)  Como algunos sin duda ya sabréis el pasado fin de semana se celebró SkeptiCamp Madrid 2012, por primera vez en un país de habla no inglesa, el primero por tanto en castellano y en España, cuya organización tuve el honor y el privilegio de coordinar y dirigir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SkeptiCamp Madrid 2012</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/01/skepticamp-madrid-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/01/skepticamp-madrid-2012/</guid>
      <description>Por algún extraño motivo no he hablado hasta ahora de uno de los proyectos a los que más tiempo de ocio (ocio puro) he dedicado en los últimos meses: la promoción en castellano a nivel global del modelo SkeptiCamp (lo que llamamos ESkeptiCamp) y en concreto la organización de SkeptiCamp Madrid 2012, que se llevará a cabo este próximo Sábado 28 de Enero en Madrid. Vayamos por partes.
¿Qué es un SkeptiCamp?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un año de ediciones en OpenStreetMap</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/01/un-ano-de-ediciones-en-openstreetmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2012/01/un-ano-de-ediciones-en-openstreetmap/</guid>
      <description>Hoy toca hablar de uno de los servicios en los que colaboro todo lo que puedo. Se trata de OpenStreetMap, la base de datos geográficos libre. Para que entiendan su necesidad, a pesar de que contamos con servicios gratuitos de mapas a patadas, es perfecto el párrafo de introducción a la Wiki del proyecto.
  OpenStreetMap creates and provides free geographic data such as street maps to anyone who wants them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crónica y Unboxing de un pedido a XKCD</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/12/cronica-y-unboxing-de-un-pedido-xkcd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/12/cronica-y-unboxing-de-un-pedido-xkcd/</guid>
      <description>Recupero la no siempre valorada (y escasamente frecuente en mi caso) costumbre de hacer una crónica del unboxing de un pedido. En esta ocasión se trata de narrar los hechos acontecidos desde que se realizó el pedido en el pasado mes de Julio hasta hoy. Todos ustedes deberían conocer la tira cómica de XKCD, y si no es así pulsen Alt-F4 en este momento. No me detendré en ello.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BoardGameGeek 2011 Secret Santa</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/11/boardgamegeek-2011-secret-santa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/11/boardgamegeek-2011-secret-santa/</guid>
      <description>(De ahora en adelante escribiré algunas de mis entradas en inglés, como simple entrenamiento y entretenimiento. A nadie le debería sorprender. Por favor, comuniquen cualquier error o incorrección)
One of the main (and marvellous) things about BoardGameGeek (BGG) is its Community. The entire website is built upon them, thanks to them. That&#39;s why I&#39;m part of it, I love it, help it grow, and cheerfully support it each year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Commons</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/02/creative-commons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2011/02/creative-commons/</guid>
      <description>Creative Commons es una organización sin ánimo de lucro fundada en 2001 por Lawrence Lessig, Hal Abelson y Eric Eldred. Está destinada a facilitar la compartición de la cultura (en todas sus formas) mediante una serie de licencias totalmente gratuitas que simplifican y amparan legalmente a todo aquel que quiera publicar algo sin reservar todos los derechos. El creador puede elegir de forma fácil y rápida qué licencia otorga a cada una de sus obras, según permita o no las obras derivadas, el uso comercial, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Brother de Cory Doctorow</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2010/05/little-brother-de-cory-doctorow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2010/05/little-brother-de-cory-doctorow/</guid>
      <description>Acabo de terminar de leerlo y en este caso no demoro (ni olvido) la reseña ya que siento la necesidad de recomendar su lectura, ya que ha llegado a mi gracias a las sugerencias de dos buenos amigos (reseña de Pablo, reseña de Angela).
Hay varias cosas interesantes e inusuales en esta novela. La temática es altamente técnica y política, siendo la obra en cada uno de sus capítulos un gran alegato a las libertades civiles y al pensamiento crítico.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>En defensa de los derechos fundamentales en Internet</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2009/12/en-defensa-de-los-derechos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2009/12/en-defensa-de-los-derechos/</guid>
      <description>Ante la inclusión en el Anteproyecto de Ley de Economía sostenible de modificaciones legislativas que afectan al libre ejercicio de las libertades de expresión, información y el derecho de acceso a la cultura a través de Internet, los periodistas, bloggers, usuarios, profesionales y creadores de internet manifestamos nuestra firme oposición al proyecto, y declaramos que:
 Los derechos de autor no pueden situarse por encima de los derechos fundamentales de los ciudadanos, como el derecho a la privacidad, a la seguridad, a la presunción de inocencia, a la tutela judicial efectiva y a la libertad de expresión.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actualizo mi Geek Code</title>
      <link>https://luiyo.net/blog/2004/10/actualizo-mi-geek-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://luiyo.net/blog/2004/10/actualizo-mi-geek-code/</guid>
      <description>Viendo a Cek publicar su Geek Code me ha recordado el mío, y paso a actualizarlo.
Mi Geek Code hace casi un año, el 01/11/2003:
-----BEGIN GEEK CODE BLOCK-----
Version: 3.12 GB/CA/L d- s+:+ a-- C++ UL++++ P+ L++ E W++ N- w+ O-- M-- V PS++ PE++ Y+ PGP- t++ 5+ X++ R tv- b++ DI++ D+ G e h! r+ y+++++**
------END GEEK CODE BLOCK------ Y ahora mismo es:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>